Wednesday, September 25, 2024

[Sign Out](javascript:newzware_doLogout();) [Sign In](javascript:void(0)) [Subscribe](https://www.kitsapdailynews.com/subscribe/) [Newsletter](https://www.kitsapdailynews.com/newsletters/) [Contact Us](https://www.kitsapdailynews.com/contact/)[](https://www.facebook.com/KitsapDailyNews/ "Find Us On Facebook")[](https://twitter.com/KitsapDailyNews/ "Find Us On Twitter")[](https://www.instagram.com/KitsapDailyNews/ "Find Us On Instagam")[](https://www.kitsapdailynews.com/feed/ "Access Our RSS Feed")

* [Sign Out](javascript:newzware_doLogout();)
* [Sign In](javascript:void(0))

[

58°F](https://www.kitsapdailynews.com/weather/ "Current weather and forecast")

Submit search 

* Submit search 

Privacy Policy
==============

_Last updated: August 22, 2024_

_This Privacy Policy describes Our policies and procedures on the collection, use, and disclosure of Your information when You use the Service and tells You about Your privacy rights and how the law protects You._

_We use Your Personal data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, You agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this Privacy Policy._

### **Interpretation and Definitions** 

##### Interpretation

The words of which the initial letter is capitalized have meanings defined under the following conditions. The following definitions shall have the same meaning regardless of whether they appear in singular or plural.

##### Definitions

For the purposes of this Privacy Policy:

* Account means a unique account created for You to access our Service or parts of our Service.
* Company (referred to as either “the Company”, “We”, “Us” or “Our” in this Agreement) refers to Sound Publishing Inc., PO Box 930, Everett, WA 98206-0930.
* Cookies are small files that are placed on Your computer, mobile device, or any other device by a website, containing the details of Your browsing history on that website among its many uses.
* Country refers to the United States
* Device means any device that can access the Service such as a computer, a cellphone, or a digital tablet.
* Personal Data is any information that relates to an identified or identifiable individual.
* Service refers to the Website.
* Service Provider means any natural or legal person who processes the data on behalf of the Company. It refers to third-party companies or individuals employed by the Company to facilitate the Service, to provide the Service on behalf of the Company, to perform services related to the Service, or to assist the Company in analyzing how the Service is used.
* Usage Data refers to data collected automatically, either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).
* Website refers to:
* Herald Net, accessible from HeraldNet.com
* Peninsula Daily News, accessible from PeninsulaDailyNews.com
* Juneau Empire, accessible from JuneauEmpire.com
* The Daily World, accessible from TheDailyWorld.com
* Kent Reporter, accessible from KentReporter.com
* Whidbey News-Times, accessible from WhidbeyNewsTimes.com
* Kitsap Daily News, accessible from KitsapDailyNews.com
* Peninsula Clarion, accessible from PeninsulaClarion.com
* Seattle Weekly, accessible from SeattleWeekly.com
* Federal Way Mirror, accessible from FederalWayMirror.com
* Bellevue Reporter, accessible from BellevueReporter.com
* Vashon-Maury Island Beachcomber, accessible from VashonBeachcomber.com
* Bainbridge Island Review, accessible from BainbridgeReview.com
* South Whidbey Record, accessible from SouthWhidbeyRecord.com
* Kirkland Reporter, accessible from KirklandReporter.com
* Auburn Reporter, accessible from Auburn-Reporter.com
* The Journal of the San Juan Islands, accessible from SanJuanJournal.com
* Islands’ Sounder, accessible from IslandsSounder.com
* Redmond Reporter, accessible from Redmond-Reporter.com
* Renton Reporter, accessible from RentonReporter.com
* Bothell-Kenmore Reporter, accessible from Bothell-Reporter.com
* Issaquah Reporter, accessible from IssaquahReporter.com
* Sequim Gazette, accessible from SequimGazette.com
* Homer News, accessible from HomerNews.com
* Enumclaw Courier-Herald, accessible from CourierHerald.com
* Mercer Island Reporter, accessible from MI-Reporter.com
* The Reporter, accessible from CovingtonReporter.com
* Snoqualmie Valley Record, accessible from ValleyRecord.com
* Forks Forum, accessible from ForksForum.com
* La Raza del Noroeste, accessible from LaRazaNW.com
* Gazette-Tribune, accessible from Gazette-Tribune.com
* Islands’ Weekly, accessible from IslandsWeekly.com
* Daily Index, accessible from TacomaDailyIndex.com
* You means the individual accessing or using the Service, or the company, or other legal entity on behalf of which such individual is accessing or using the Service, as applicable.

Collecting and Using Your Personal Data
=======================================

### **Types of Data Collected**

##### Personal Data

While using Our Service, We may ask You to provide Us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify You. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:

* Email address
* First name and last name
* Phone number
* Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City
* Usage Data

##### Your Rights and Choices

The CCPA provides consumers (California Residents) with specific rights regarding their personal information. This section describes your CCPA rights and explains how to exercise those rights.

You have the right to request that Sound Publishing Inc, disclose certain information to you about our collection and use of your personal information over the past 12 months. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request, we will disclose to you:

* Which personal information is being collected
* Whether your personal data is being sold or shared, and to whom
* Access one’s own personal information

You have:

* The right to equal service and price, even for consumers who exercise their privacy rights.
* The right to object to the sale of personal data

To exercise the access, data portability, and deletion rights described above, please submit a verifiable consumer request to us by either:

* Calling us at: (360) 394-5800
* Emailing us at: [contact@soundpublishing.com](mailto:contact@soundpublishing.com)

Only you, or a person registered with the California Secretary of State that you authorize to act on your behalf, may make a verifiable consumer request related to your personal information. You may also make a verifiable consumer request on behalf of your minor child.

You may only make a verifiable consumer request for access or data portability twice within a 12-month period. The verifiable consumer request must:

* Provide sufficient information that allows us to reasonably verify you are the person from whom we collected personal information or an authorized representative.
* Describe your request with sufficient detail that allows us to properly understand, evaluate, and respond to it.

Personal Information Sales Opt-Out and Opt-In Rights. You have the right to direct us to not sell your personal information at any time (the “right to opt-out”). Consumers who opt-in to personal information sales may opt-out of future sales at any time. To exercise the right to opt out, you (or your authorized representative) may submit a request to us by clicking here: [**Do Not Sell My Personal Information**](http://www.soundpublishing.com/contact/) **(**[**http://www.soundpublishing.com/contact/**](http://www.soundpublishing.com/contact/)**).** Once you make an opt-out request, we will wait at least twelve (12) months before asking you to reauthorize personal information sales. However, you may change your mind and opt back into personal information sales at any time by: http://www.soundpublishing.com/contact/. You do not need to create an account with us to exercise your opt-out rights. We will only use personal information provided in an opt-out request to review and comply with the request.

##### Usage Data

Usage Data is collected automatically when using the Service.

Usage Data may include information such as Your Device’s Internet Protocol address (e.g., IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that You visit, the time and date of Your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

When You access the Service by or through a mobile device, We may collect certain information automatically, including, but not limited to, the type of mobile device You use, Your mobile device’s unique ID, the IP address of Your mobile device, Your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browser You use, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

We may also collect information that Your browser sends whenever You visit our Service or when You access the Service by or through a mobile device.

##### Tracking Technologies and Cookies

We use Cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on Our Service and store certain information. Tracking technologies used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze Our Service. The technologies We use may include:

* Cookies or Browser Cookies. A cookie is a small file placed on Your Device. You can instruct Your browser to refuse all Cookies or to indicate when a Cookie is being sent. However, if You do not accept Cookies, You may not be able to use some parts of our Service. Unless you have adjusted Your browser setting so that it will refuse Cookies, our Service may use Cookies.
* Flash Cookies. Certain features of our Service may use locally stored objects (or Flash Cookies) to collect and store information about Your preferences or Your activity on our Service. Flash Cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as those used for Browser Cookies. For more information on how You can delete Flash Cookies, please read “Where can I change the settings for disabling, or deleting local shared objects?” available at [https://helpx.adobe.com/flash-player/kb/disable-local-shared-objects-flash.html#main\_Where\_can\_I\_change\_the\_settings\_for\_disabling\_\_or\_deleting\_local\_shared\_objects\_](https://helpx.adobe.com/flash-player/kb/disable-local-shared-objects-flash.html#main_Where_can_I_change_the_settings_for_disabling__or_deleting_local_shared_objects_)
* Web Beacons. Certain sections of our Service and our emails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an email and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of a certain section and verifying system and server integrity).

Cookies can be “Persistent” or “Session” Cookies. Persistent Cookies remain on Your personal computer or mobile device when You go offline, while Session Cookies are deleted as soon as You close Your web browser. Learn more about cookies: [What Are Cookies?](https://www.privacypolicies.com/blog/cookies/)

We use both Session and Persistent Cookies for the purposes set out below:

* Necessary / Essential Cookies
* Type: Session Cookies
* Administered by: Us
* Purpose: These Cookies are essential to provide You with services available through the Website and to enable You to use some of its features. They help to authenticate users and prevent fraudulent use of user accounts. Without these Cookies, the services that You have asked for cannot be provided, and We only use these Cookies to provide You with those services.
* Cookies Policy / Notice Acceptance Cookies
* Type: Persistent Cookies
* Administered by: Us
* Purpose: These Cookies identify if users have accepted the use of cookies on the Website.
* Functionality Cookies
* Type: Persistent Cookies
* Administered by: Us
* Purpose: These Cookies allow us to remember choices You make when You use the Website, such as remembering your login details or language preference. The purpose of these Cookies is to provide You with a more personal experience and to avoid You having to re-enter your preferences every time You use the Website.
* Tracking and Performance Cookies
* Type: Persistent Cookies
* Administered by: Third Parties
* Purpose: These Cookies are used to track information about traffic to the Website and how users use the Website. The information gathered via these Cookies may directly or indirectly identify you as an individual visitor. This is because the information collected is typically linked to a pseudonymous identifier associated with the device you use to access the Website. We may also use these Cookies to test new pages, features, or new functionality of the Website to see how our users react to them.
* Targeting and Advertising Cookies
* Type: Persistent Cookies
* Administered by: Third Parties
* Purpose: These Cookies track your browsing habits to enable Us to show advertising which is more likely to be of interest to You. These Cookies use information about your browsing history to group You with other users who have similar interests. Based on that information, and with Our permission, third-party advertisers can place Cookies to enable them to show adverts that We think will be relevant to your interests while You are on third-party websites.

For more information about the cookies we use and your choices regarding cookies, please visit our Cookies Policy or the Cookies section of our Privacy Policy.

##### Use of Your Personal Data

The Company may use Personal Data for the following purposes:

* To provide and maintain our Service, including monitoring the usage of our Service.
* To manage Your Account: to manage Your registration as a user of the Service. The Personal Data You provide can give You access to different functionalities of the Service that are available to You as a registered user.
* For the performance of a contract: the development, compliance, and undertaking of the purchase contract for the products, items, or services You have purchased or of any other contract with Us through the Service.
* To contact You: To contact You by email, telephone calls, SMS, or other equivalent forms of electronic communication, such as a mobile application’s push notifications regarding updates or informative communications related to the functionalities, products, or contracted services, including the security updates, when necessary or reasonable for their implementation.
* To provide You with news, special offers, and general information about other goods, services, and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless You have opted not to receive such information.
* To manage Your requests: To attend to and manage Your requests to Us.
* To deliver targeted advertising to You: We may use Your information to develop and display content and advertising (and work with third-party vendors who do so) tailored to Your interests and/or location and to measure its effectiveness.
* For business transfers: We may use Your information to evaluate or conduct a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of Our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which Personal Data held by Us about our Service users is among the assets transferred.
* For other purposes: We may use Your information for other purposes, such as data analysis, identifying usage trends, determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns, and evaluating and improving our Service, products, services, marketing, and your experience.
* We may also use Your information for (1) the development of any software program, model, algorithm, or other generative AI tool, including, but not limited to, training or using the Content in connection with the development or operation of a machine learning or artificial intelligence (AI) system (including any use of the Content for training, fine tuning, or grounding the machine learning or AI system or as part of retrieval-augmented generation); or (2) providing archived or cached data sets containing Content to another person or entity.

We may share Your personal information in the following situations:

* With Service Providers: We may share Your personal information with Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service, to show advertisements to You to help support and maintain Our Service, to advertise on third-party websites to You after You visited our Service, and to contact You.
* For business transfers: We may share or transfer Your personal information in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of Company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of Our business to another company.
* With Affiliates: We may share Your information with Our affiliates, in which case we will require those affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy. Affiliates include Our parent company and any other subsidiaries, joint venture partners, or other companies that We control or that are under common control with Us.
* With business partners: We may share Your information with Our business partners to offer You certain products, services, or promotions.
* With other users: when You share personal information or otherwise interact in public areas with other users, such information may be viewed by all users and may be publicly distributed outside.
* With Your consent: We may disclose Your personal information for any other purpose with Your consent.

##### Retention of Your Personal Data

The Company will retain Your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use Your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.

The Company will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of Our Service, or We are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.

##### Transfer of Your Personal Data

Your information, including Personal Data, is processed at the Company’s operating offices and in any other places where the parties involved in the processing are located. It means that this information may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of Your state, province, country, or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from Your jurisdiction.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by Your submission of such information represents Your agreement to that transfer.

The Company will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that Your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of Your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of Your data and other personal information.

### **Disclosure of Your Personal Data**

##### Business Transactions

If the Company is involved in a merger, acquisition, or asset sale, Your Personal Data may be transferred. We will provide notice before Your Personal Data is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.

##### Law enforcement

Under certain circumstances, the Company may be required to disclose Your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g., a court or a government agency).

##### Other legal requirements

The Company may disclose Your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

* Comply with a legal obligation
* Protect and defend the rights or property of the Company
* Prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
* Protect the personal safety of Users of the Service or the public
* Protect against legal liability

##### Security of Your Personal Data

The security of Your Personal Data is important to Us but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While We strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect Your Personal Data, We cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### **Detailed Information on the Processing of Your Personal Data**

The Service Providers We use may have access to Your Personal Data. These third-party vendors collect, store, use, process, and transfer information about Your activity on Our Service in accordance with their Privacy Policies.

##### Analytics

We may use third-party Service providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.

* Google Analytics
* Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.
* You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.
* For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: [https://policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy)
* Google Ad Manager
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en)
* LiveIntent
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www.liveintent.com/privacy-policy/](https://www.liveintent.com/privacy-policy/)
* Google Tag Manager
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en)
* Mather
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www.mathereconomics.com/privacy-policy/](https://www.mathereconomics.com/privacy-policy/)
* Metrics For News
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www.metricsfornews.com/?page=privacy](https://www.metricsfornews.com/?page=privacy)

##### Advertising

We may use Service Providers to show advertisements to You to help support and maintain Our Service.

* Google AdSense & DoubleClick Cookie
* Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our Service. Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our Service or other websites on the Internet.
* You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick Cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the Google Ads Settings web page: [http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/)
* Sovrn
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www.sovrn.com/legal/privacy-policy/](https://www.sovrn.com/legal/privacy-policy/)
* Teads
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www.teads.com/teads-website-privacy-policy/](https://www.teads.com/teads-website-privacy-policy/)
* District M
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www.districtm.net/privacy-policy/](https://www.districtm.net/privacy-policy/)
* EMX
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://enginemediaexchange.com/privacy/](https://enginemediaexchange.com/privacy/)
* Sonobi
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://sonobi.com/privacy-policy/](https://sonobi.com/privacy-policy/)
* Conversant
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www.epsilon.com/us/privacy-policy](https://www.epsilon.com/us/privacy-policy)
* Amazon
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=468496&ref\_=footer\_privacy](https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=468496&ref_=footer_privacy)
* Google AdX
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy)
* GumGum
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://gumgum.com/terms-and-policies/privacy-policy](https://gumgum.com/terms-and-policies/privacy-policy)
* 33Across
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www1.33across.com/privacy-policy/](https://www1.33across.com/privacy-policy/)
* Automated
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://automatad.com/privacy-policy.php](https://automatad.com/privacy-policy.php)
* Pulsepoint
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://pulsepoint.com/legal/platform-privacy-policy](https://pulsepoint.com/legal/platform-privacy-policy)
* Appnexus
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www.xandr.com/privacy/](https://www.xandr.com/privacy/)
* Verizon Media
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www.verizon.com/about/privacy/full-privacy-policy](https://www.verizon.com/about/privacy/full-privacy-policy)
* OpenX
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www.openx.com/legal/privacy-policy/](https://www.openx.com/legal/privacy-policy/)
* Justpremium
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://justpremium.com/terms-conditions/](https://justpremium.com/terms-conditions/)
* ATD Adx
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy)
* IndexExchange
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www.indexexchange.com/privacy/](https://www.indexexchange.com/privacy/)
* Synacor
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://synacor.com/privacy-policy/default.aspx](https://synacor.com/privacy-policy/default.aspx)
* Nobid
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www.nobid.io/privacy-policy/](https://www.nobid.io/privacy-policy/)
* Smartadserver
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://smartadserver.com/corporate-privacy-policy](https://smartadserver.com/corporate-privacy-policy)
* Index Exchange
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www.indexexchange.com/privacy/](https://www.indexexchange.com/privacy/)
* Luna Media
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://lunamedia.io/privacy-policy/](https://lunamedia.io/privacy-policy/)
* Connatix
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www.connatix.com/privacy-policy](https://www.connatix.com/privacy-policy)
* RTB House
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www.rtbhouse.com/privacy-center/website-privacy-policy/](https://www.rtbhouse.com/privacy-center/website-privacy-policy/)
* Outbrain
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www.outbrain.com/legal/privacy#privacy-policy](https://www.outbrain.com/legal/privacy#privacy-policy)
* Plus
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://ad.plus/privacy-policy](https://ad.plus/privacy-policy)
* Next Millennium
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://nextmillennium.io/privacy-policy/](https://nextmillennium.io/privacy-policy/)
* Rubicon
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://rubiconproject.com/rubicon-project-advertising-technology-privacy-policy/](https://rubiconproject.com/rubicon-project-advertising-technology-privacy-policy/)
* PubMatic
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://pubmatic.com/legal/privacy/](https://pubmatic.com/legal/privacy/)
* RhythmOne
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www.rhythmone.com/privacy-policy/](https://www.rhythmone.com/privacy-policy/)
* YeldMo
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://yieldmo.com/privacy-policy/](https://yieldmo.com/privacy-policy/)
* Undertone
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www.undertone.com/privacy/](https://www.undertone.com/privacy/)
* TripleLift
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://triplelift.com/privacy/](https://triplelift.com/privacy/)
* 152Media
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://152media.com/privacy-policy/](https://152media.com/privacy-policy/)
* OneTag
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www.onetag.com/privacy/](https://www.onetag.com/privacy/)
* ShareThrough
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www.sharethrough.com/privacy-center](https://www.sharethrough.com/privacy-center)
* AdYouLike
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www.adyoulike.com/pages/privacy](https://www.adyoulike.com/pages/privacy)
* DistrictM
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [net/privacy-policy/](https://www.privacypolicies.com/live/districtm.net/privacy-policy/)
* Teads
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www.teads.com/teads-website-privacy-policy/](https://www.teads.com/teads-website-privacy-policy/)
* LoopMe
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://legal.loopme.com/privacy-center](https://legal.loopme.com/privacy-center)
* Facebook
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://about.facebook.com/actions/protecting-privacy-and-security](https://about.facebook.com/actions/protecting-privacy-and-security)
* The MediaGrid
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www.iponweb.com/policies-legal/themediagrid-privacy-policy/](https://www.iponweb.com/policies-legal/themediagrid-privacy-policy/)
* Impactify
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://impactify.io/privacy-policy/](https://impactify.io/privacy-policy/)
* AdaptMX
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://adaptmx.com/privacy-policy/](https://adaptmx.com/privacy-policy/)
* AdPone
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://adpone.com/privacy-policy/](https://adpone.com/privacy-policy/)
* Kargo
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://kargo.com/websiteprivacy](https://kargo.com/websiteprivacy)

##### Email Marketing

We may use Your Personal Data to contact You with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials, and other information that may be of interest to You. You may opt-out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from Us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email We send or by contacting Us.

We may use Email Marketing Service Providers to manage and send emails to You.

* WhatCounts
* Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www.whatcounts.com/privacy-policy/](https://www.whatcounts.com/privacy-policy/)

##### Behavioral Remarketing

The Company uses remarketing services to advertise to You after You accessed or visited our Service. We and Our third-party vendors use cookies and non-cookie technologies to help Us recognize Your Device and understand how You use our Service so that We can improve our Service to reflect Your interests and serve You advertisements that are likely to be of more interest to You.

These third-party vendors collect, store, use, process, and transfer information about Your activity on Our Service in accordance with their Privacy Policies and to enable Us to:

* Measure and analyze traffic and browsing activity on Our Service
* Show advertisements for our products and/or services to You on third-party websites or apps
* Measure and analyze the performance of Our advertising campaigns

Some of these third-party vendors may use non-cookie technologies that may not be impacted by browser settings that block cookies. Your browser may not permit You to block such technologies. You can use the following third-party tools to decline the collection and use of information for the purpose of serving You interest-based advertising:

* The NAI’s opt-out platform: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)
* The EDAA’s opt-out platform [http://www.youronlinechoices.com/](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/)
* The DAA’s opt-out platform: [http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN](http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN)

You may opt-out of all personalized advertising by enabling privacy features on Your mobile device such as Limit Ad Tracking (iOS) and Opt Out of Ads Personalization (Android). See Your mobile device Help system for more information.

We may share information, such as hashed email addresses (if available) or other online identifiers collected on Our Service with these third-party vendors. This allows Our third-party vendors to recognize and deliver Your ads across devices and browsers. To read more about the technologies used by these third-party vendors and their cross-device capabilities please refer to the Privacy Policy of each vendor listed below.

The third-party vendors We use are:

* Google Ads (AdWords)
* Google Ads (AdWords) remarketing service is provided by Google Inc.
* You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page: [http://www.google.com/settings/ads](http://www.google.com/settings/ads)
* Google also recommends installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on – [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) – for your web browser. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics.
* For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: [https://policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy)
* Facebook
* Facebook remarketing service is provided by Facebook Inc.
* You can learn more about interest-based advertising from Facebook by visiting this page: [https://www.facebook.com/help/516147308587266](https://www.facebook.com/help/516147308587266)
* To opt-out of Facebook’s interest-based ads, follow these instructions from Facebook: [https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217](https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217)
* Facebook adheres to the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising established by the Digital Advertising Alliance. You can also opt-out of Facebook and other participating companies through the Digital Advertising Alliance in the USA [http://www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/), the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada in Canada [http://youradchoices.ca/](http://youradchoices.ca/) or the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance in Europe [http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/), or opt-out using your mobile device settings.
* For more information on the privacy practices of Facebook, please visit Facebook’s Data Policy: [https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation)

### **Children’s Privacy**

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If You are a parent or guardian and You are aware that Your child has provided Us with Personal Data, without your consent, please contact Us. If We become aware that We have collected Personal Data from anyone under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, We take steps to remove that information from Our servers.

If We need to rely on consent as a legal basis for processing Your information and Your country requires consent from a parent, We may require Your parent’s consent before We collect and use that information.

### **Links to Other Websites**

Our Service may contain links to other websites that are not operated by Us. If You click on a third-party link, You will be directed to that third-party’s site. We strongly advise You to review the Privacy Policy of every site You visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.

### **Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We may update Our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify You of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

We will let You know via email and/or a prominent notice on Our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the “Last updated” date at the top of this Privacy Policy.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

### **Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, You can contact us by phone number (360) 394-5800.

### Sign Up For Our Newsletters

#### Subscribe to our e-mail newsletter to receive updates.

Featured Local Savings
----------------------

Quicklinks

About Us

© 2024 Kitsap Daily News + [Sound Publishing](https://www.soundpublishing.com/) + [Black Press Media](https://www.blackpressmedia.com/). All Rights Reserved.

Powered By [NewzBoost](https://www.newzboost.com/)

Please ensure Javascript is enabled for purposes of [website accessibility](https://userway.org/)
